Gather round, come take a look...
It's time for Theatre of Darkness.
Pumpkin Field
This is spending the summer vacation at grandmother's house.
A story of an elementary school student.
Why am I the only one who has to go to Grandma's place?
it can't be helped.
Your mom is having a hard time because her belly is so big.
I know, but...
Ah, fell out.
Oh.
Then bury it in the field.
Field?
That's the rule around here.
Hurry up before you lose it.
Ok.
Huh?
Who's there?
What is it?
It's too boring and...
i can't go back to Tokyo.
Because my little brother is about to be born.
Ah, i see.
If you're free, let's play together.
Is it evening already? I have to head home.
See you tomorrow.
Se-See you tomorrow.
I'm leaving!
Have a nice day.
Hey!
I'm here!
There’s nothing going on, but
Every day like this is not bad.
Time flies while you're having fun.
It might be even more fun if I had siblings.
You're heading back to your home in Tokyo soon, right?
i don't want to go home.
I wish summer vacation would never end.
Shall I grant it to you?
Huh?
Exchange for something important.
But there's nothing I can give you.
You have.
Something very important.
come on, let's exchange.
Was it this field wide like that before?
Ahhh!
Yuta!
Grandma...
Thanks God.
I made it in time.
Grandma...
It's okay now.
Let's home.
Uh?
Grandma?
Ah...
It's a good thing it didn't amount to anything worse than this.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
It's ok...
THE END